(Even it's in the gaster * water)
What's up on earth
That...
Don't be shy,
be quick to tell me it clearly
But...
We'll be glad to consult with you
you may say that if you like
Then I'll say that boldly, It's so...
I ate peanuts at home just now
But...
Did you eat a stone?
I remembered it's in the direction
You're wrong, it's nearby
What's mum looking for
It's opal
It fall down from the ring only just
Then I ate
I heard its value's 500, 000 Yuan
Shizuka--'
There're 500, 000 Yuan
in Shizuka's belly
What shall I do?
Doraemon,
be quick to take the prop out
For example, they're the saw
and the sellotape
Shizuka
Don't flee, you'll not be cut
Really
Don't worry
Is it OK
This is...
I found
It's the submarine
What will you use it to do
We'll drive it
We'll use the narrowing lamp
to make the submarine diminish
Then I know
we'll fetch the opal out
from Shizuka's mouth to her belly
Nobita and Doraemon will enter
Shizuka's mouth
It's too cool
Aren't you agree?
Will you have any else ideas, Shizuka?
Sorry, I beg you
OK, start at once
ls it OK as long as I can see it
Right, lamp the whole submarine
Will I eat this really
Right, quickly
What's the matter with you, Shizuka?
It seems that it's terrible
Don't pick fault, be quick
Oh, my dear! The water's too rapid!
Lie down, quickly
It's changed now
Shizuka, can you hear
We're going through your gullet
Don't move
The submarine doesn't work easily
If it doesn't work, we'll not go out
Don't horrify me
Where's here
Ah, it's belly
There're many scraps of peanuts
Shizuka didn't chaw them well
They're green peppers and
red radishes which I hate most
Shut up, be quick to look for the opal
Don't move
Aren't you afraid we'll not go out
Sorry, I'll not move
It seems that it's there
We'll reach there
I found it
It's that
We succeed
Go back quickly
This submarine may jump into
the nearest water
It's very convenient
We'll go, jump
Ah!
It's in the cup
Shizuka is sleeping
We'll jump into the larger place
An important success,
the submarine turns bigger
Why doesn't the opal change
Don't think too much
Give it to Shizuka quickly
OK!
What's the matter with you, Shizuka?
Aunt, excuse me, may I lie down
Sure
Then you may lie down slowly
Haven't you found the opal
She didn't notice that we've come out
Nobita, tell me the instance quickly
It's very interesting,
we'll go there again
Shizuka, it's terrible,
the submarine don't work
What? What does it mean
Will you stay in my body forever
Wait a minute, don't worry,
it's not so terrible
If we can succeed,
the submarine will move with food
From the small intestine
to the large intestine
From the large intestine to...
I think we'll go out tomorrow
Damn, No
It's a joke just now
Here you are, it's opal
Odium, Nobita, you're a boob
Sorry
Damn...
It's my fault, wait a moment...
The rubber's eaten
No problem, Nobita
Nobita...
Sorry, it's my turn this time
I don't want to go there
Don't say that
Be quick to take it out, Shizuka
(Channel of Dream)
Doraemon, do you wake up
What're you doing
I'm sleeping well
I can't be asleep
Think a way out for me
I'm sorry
Because you napped too much
I fell vapid
You may watch TV alone
It's over
Nobita, you're really a trouble maker
I said that it's over
This TV is very special
Ah, it's broadcasting
The monster program's still being
broadcasted what's the channel?
Channel of dream
Ah! ? Help
I appeared in the TV program
Help! Help!
What? It's very shameful
I didn't appear in the TV program
Doraemon, what's the matter
The just herald named Jian came here
He appeared finally
I'll be saved
I'm a good friend of weak men
You saved me, please sign
What program is this
Doraemon, are you angry
It's too noisy
But this is Jian's dream, no way
The TV may see others' dream
It's too vapid, is there
only this channel
If you estimate the right direction
and distance, you may find all dreams
I'll go to sleep, don't make a noise
OK, I'll look at Suneo's dream
I'm crying again
It's too ugly
Why? Everyone lets me play this role
The lesson's too difficult to work out
I'm the same with you
Me too
Boob!
It's so easy but you can't work it out
I'll punish you 80 times
Help!
Stand there, don't run
What a pain
Stop
Teacher can't punish student terribly
You're Suneo
ls this man Suneo?
Do you want to work out this question?
I beg you, Suneo
OK, let me manage it
It's impossible even you're very smart
Teacher, what's your opinion about this
This is...
Do you give in?
I went down to you
You're too excellent
Suneo is emulative
What're you doing
I don't know who has a good dream
Let's look at Shizuka's dream
It's really different from others
It's like fairy tale of foreign soil
The backgrounds dreamlike
I was attacked and imprisoned
in the fortress by genie
But I believe
my prince will come to save me
It's very interesting, I'll appear
as a prince at this time
Why are you riding a pig, Nobita?
I'm afraid of horse
What? Terrible!
What's that?
The genie came back
Damn, I'm afraid of the evil genie
Odium
Cheer up
It lost face
Even Shizuka let me act the dastard
Wait a minute
Wait a minute, Shizuka
I hate this thing
Damn!
Terrible
The dream realized
Doraemon, get rid of it quickly
No way, they can't be gone away
Help me, Doraemon
Hurry, or you'll be treaded
But I can't move
OK, let me draw away the genie
Take the chance to flee quickly
But...
It settled, sorry, thank you
I'll go, see you, Doraemon
Don't look down upon me
What're you doing? What a pain
Doraemon,
I'll remember you for ever, so long
To have the dream is egregious
It's time to go to school
but I'll not wake you up
I'll not take care of you
Help
I'm afraid of genie
It's too terrible
(Development and degradation radiation)
ls it funny on earth
Damn, it's too much
Why is my father so outmoded
Every day is developing
but he doesn't catch up
If it goes on, he'll be abandoned
What're you saying on earth
Listen to me, Doraemon
This radio
Nobody uses it now
Others have the radios with tapes
I let him buy a new one
but my father said
if radio would be heard, it'd be OK
Children whose parents have
such old thought are hard-working
In a word, you want to have a new radio
Develop and degrade radiation
I want to have a radio
It all depends on me
Haw, it'll be OK if it's
adjusted ten years backward
It's the neotype radio
Great
Develop it again to have a look
incidentally
Right
It's a watch radio
Nobody used this kind of radio
Fantastic
And there's a TV on it
It may degrade too
Give it to me
It's the first radio
It's very interesting
Please lend it to me
Doraemon
But you can't take it for special use
I know
Well, what will we develop
Let us look at the pencil first
Set the evolution button
Move!
It's auto pencil
If you use microphone to talk
it'll write what you said
What's your opinion
Great, I don't know
what the light will become
It disappeared
The ceiling and wall can give out light
Look
the door became the auto door
OK, I'll let my family develop
Wait, don't do that
I'll use it to find
the progenitor of living beings
to know how it evolved
Living beings? That's so
My father's thought is too old
I'll let him become a future man
But...
It doesn't matter
Is it OK
It'll be good to my father
Nix!
It'll be broken
Terrible
It got the degeneration
Be quick to turn back
Oh, my dear!
What're you doing, Nobita?
Nothing
It's too dangerous,
let's do a animal experiment first
Which one can fit...
Maybe it's OK
I don't know what Nobita's doing
I found it finally
Right, Doraemon's afraid of mouse
That's OK,
let us look at the progenitor of mice
As if its body became bigger
This is the progenitor of rodents
They evolved into bunns and lapins
The progenitors of mammalias
came from reptilians
two hundred million years ago
The mammals of reptilians
Reptilians
They're the most primal
It must be become the mouse
Help! Help! Damn!
Hist, go there
Don't come here
Nobita, don't joke
It's too terrible,
there's a dinosaur in my dream
I want to look at it too
An important thing happened
How to do
Doraemon, how to do
I've a good idea
Make the mousetrap develop
It went to find quarries alone
I succeeded
Nobita
I said that you didn't use it rashly
Sorry
Use it again, let my father develop
The mind's too powerful,
the head got bigger
Because
he depended on the machine too much
The hands and feet degraded
In order not to suck the dirty air
his vibrissas turned longer too
Nobita,
what's the matter with your mother
(Super Armor)
Pardon me... Pardon me...
It's too noisy, you guy
Bastard
Help me, Doraemon
Don't be egregious, Nobita
You always rely on me
It doesn't matter,
you'd use your strength
Although what you said is right...
Jian's fist's terrible
If he beats you once
You'll become dazzle
If I have an armor,
I may fight against him
Do me a favour, Doraemon
I'll keep your help in mind forever
Since you said so
I'll bring out the armor
The armor ranking first in space
Where's it?
I saw nothing
Let me tell you, idiot can't find it
And it doesn't work
when an idiot put it on
Nobita isn't so stupid
I can see it
Wow, what a great armor
I like the color best
Let me help you put it on
I'm glad that you like it
I'll not worry when I put it on
I'll go to beat Jian
Beat him
Wait, I don't know you'll mean business
Do you know the story of
The New Clothes Of The Emperor
Nobita, I'm kidding
You'll be terribly beaten
Nobita
Are you really wearing it?
I feel no...
Shizuka
Have you seen the armor?
Sure, Nobita,
your question's a little strange
It's true
Wait,
if I can't see it, won't I be a fool?
I'm not smart originally
It doesn't matter
But it'll be troublesome if I'm so
stupid that I can't see the armor
Let's confirm it first
There's a ball coming ahead
There's a hawkbill above
You wasted me a good test chance
Boring
But I won't escape
I'll test the armor's function
You can bite if you like
Xisha, it's time for meal
The feeling is complex
Bros, I'm sorry Beat me with your club
OK?
I beg you
It's nothing
I'm not wounded
It's great
It's air mallet,
of course it's not painful
Did you see Jian
I'll report he beat me just now
Please tell him when you see him
that I'll teach him a lesson
I heard Nobita will fight against Jian
ls it true?
Hey, I heard they'd struggle
against each other
Really?
I heard there'd be a battle
between them
Nobita, you'll be killed, Nobita
What? Who said that?
I'll not forgive him, keep off
You'd better be careful
The timid dares to say that,
there must be some problem
After hearing what you said,
I really feel curious
Doraemon supports him
Did Doraemon give him a good weapon
He can kill you...
I've been waiting for you long, Jian
Come over now
Really, it must be so
What's up, Jian
It's not like you, are you scared
Nobita, I was wrong just now, sorry
Oops?
Let's make it up
You're a good guy
Let's make friends
OK?
Good... I don't like fighting either
I've one question to ask you
It's so...so...
You're in super armor
I want to have a try
OK
Hah...
Take it
It fits you well, Jian
Really
OK, try it on
Nobita, beat me hard
I want to announce at first
the armor is useless to an idiot
I'll know if I'm an idiot
after I put it on
Look carefully, everybody
Jian, Let's stop
It's too noisy, shut up
Nobita, beat me hard
Then I'll begin
Indolent, it's indolent, it's painful...
It's indolent, right?
Yeah...
Nobita
I can't stand
(Hot Spring Travel)
I want jump down
No
Let's change the place
OK
What a great mountain
This is the peak of Himalayas
Golly~ You're kidding
The snow and the wind is so strong
that I can see nothing
This is the scene of the spaceship
Cool
What
One aerolite is coming
It's film, it doesn't matter
It's true to nature
Let's go to a quiet place
Ah, here's...
Sahara Desert
There's sand around, it's too quiet
I'm sleepy
ls it a film
The African jungle
It's nice
Sorry, let me hide
Help
Dearm, don't run into Nobita's room
listen to me
I didn't run
Don't be surprised,
there's a leopard there
Where?
It's strange...
Dear, don't say that
I see
You want the family to travel to
the hot spring in vacation
But at that time
There'll be many people to take train,
to live in the hotel, it's too tied
I want to be tired sometimes
I want to travel too But it seems
dad's under the harrow
What dad said is reasonable
Help him
Right, we've the film of the hot spring
Great, great
Let's dive into it
Hah!
What a pain...
What're you doing
This is the steric film
of indoor travel machine
I forget it It's painful...
We can't swim in the spring,
it's not interesting
It's OK to take this to the bathroom
Right, you'll have the sense then
There're many machines
Put them in the corridor
and other rooms too
Let's make our home a grand hotel
I want to go too
If it can be booked now...
No, if you're careful,
you'll have the chance
OK, we arrived at the hot spring
What's the matter
ls it a film?
And the leopard just now too?
It's true to nature
It's painful
There's a unseen wall here
It seems very large, in fact
it's still our narrow home
Move slowly
There's a door, is it the living room?
Come over, please come in
It's great
Fantastic
5,000 Yuan one night
It's cheap
I forget to tidy up the table
In fact the place is small
Don't always say that
We'll get to the big bathhouse
Where's the bathroom?
Here, there's a door
Ah, it's wrong
The toilet's here,
and the bathroom's here
OK, please come in
It's a pity that we can't walk freely
But the Tone's fine
Let's enjoy ourselves in the hot water~
It's comfortable
I'm expecting the grand dinner
Impossible, it's not a real hotel
Right
I feel disappointed to cook myself
You're right
Shall we order a out-sale
Yeah, there're beer and juice at home
Thank you for coming
Ah!
Is here Nobita's?
What's the matter with you
ls here Nobita's?
Yeah, what's up?
It's surprising!
Thank you
Ah?
It's not good to scare so many people
Recover the door
What, Nobita's home becomes a hotel?
Right, it becomes a hotel
Good
What, it doesn't change at all
Go inside
It's not like a hotel
You' re a maker
I'm busy, don't talk nonsense
It's curious
Ah? The switch near the door
isn't turned on
It'll have no Tone
I remember I've seen it
It changed!
It's good generally, but it's only...
What?
It's too quiet, it's no Tone
OK, it'll come
Sorry, you came to the wrong room
We've the film of the travel delegation
It's true to nature
There's a banquet next to our room
OK, great
I'm drunk, it's comfortable
It seems you're satisfied with it
Excuse me, you'd strike a balance
15,000 Yuan altogether
I feel better and better, good
We earned!
Let's share it
Isn't it a film
We were cheated by them
Wait, return my pocket money
(If Jian's a superman)
What cloak it is
I see It's Doraemon
who put it in the sun
You may become a superman
if you put it on
Have a try
Don't touch others' belongings
Sorry
Right, what's the kind of the cloak
It can make a man become a superman
Really
Lend it to me
No way
No
You're so mean
It's OK to be mean
Give it to me! No
Lend it to me... No...
Nobita
I borrowed it!
Nobita, I'm doing good to you,
it's dull to become a superman
No
To be a superman is very cool
It's painful
What? Can I become a superman
after putting it on?
Let me have a try
I put it on
I'm a superman now
It's really bad
It's cheap, it can't make you stronger
What? It can't make me stronger?
And can't fly in the sky either?
He can't fly as fast as plane...
What're you doing, tell me clearly
weather I can fly or not
You can fly
It's painful...
Tell me, Doraemon, how can I fly
If some play the flute to ask for help
you can fly
Really, OK
OK, play the flute there
I see
It flies
It's OK to fly
I'm strong enough originally
Distribute the flutes to others,
and let them call me
Do it now
Call me quickly
I envy him
Jian became a superman, I envy him
He's not worthy of being envied,
you'll see then
Will Jian fly over if we play the flute
I don't hope he comes
Who wants to see the superman,
come to get your flute
Come to get your flute
Superman...
I'm jealous of him
I want to be a superman too
HEY
Nobita,
I become a superman difficultly
But nobody call me What's the matter
Because... nothing happened
Go to find it
It's not easy to find it
It's troublesome
Nobita, Jian cursed my on the phone
He said he'd beat me
if there's no such thing
I received the call just now too
It's troublesome
Why did I meet such a thing
Nobita, it's all because that
you made the trouble
How will you compensate me
Help, help
Lalala, the superman turn out
The justice superman
Suneo, do you want to destroy the earth
I come to teach you a lesson
Help"
It's the sound of the flute
He's asking for help to superman
Hurry UP
The superman's very busy...
Jian's satisfied with his job
He'll be tired of it soon
Because when there's a sound of flute
he'll go to help
He's called when he's at table
This time he's bathing
It's OK to unchain the cloak
No, you must finish 100 piece of work
after you put it on
It's poor
You're looking for me? It's very late
It runs again
He wants to be cursed
You cheat me
to put on the strange cloak
I didn't cheat you,
you want to put it on yourself
Don't be wordy
Stop, I beg you, no
You cheated me
What do you have to ask superman
Beat Jian who bully me
OK, let me manage it
What'll we do in the future?
(Mouse And Bomb)
What's up, be calm
You're an adult
It appears
It's shameful they do like that
Mouse!
Mouse...
Help
Egregious, he dares say that
It's troublesome
The mousetrap's useless now
I've an idea
Ask Doraemon to bring out the
mousetrap of 21st century
It's dangerous
Sorry, I thought it was a mouse
when I heard mouse
I'll tremble
I want to kill them early
and make space peaceful again
Let's call it a deal
But what'll we do
You'd fight with your weapon
Fight?
Nobita, take the blue wave gun
Blue wave gun?
Mom take the hotline gun
Hotline gun?
The blue wave gun can destroy
the truck with one bullet
And the hotline gun
can melt the rebar in a second
The enemy may surprise anytime
Be careful
Good luck to you
He's exaggerating
Yeah, to use this at home
He'd have a better way
I'll go to ask Doraemon
HEY
Does the mouse appear
Hey, why do you attack us
You'd not scare me
But you'd not fire
It's too noisy, shut up
Be careful if you don't want to die
What're you saying
Will you fight?
Ah kill!
It's painful...
Nobita, he's excited now,
it's better not resist him now
He's not in...
Where did he hide
He's not here either
Come out! Don't hide! Come out!
You still didn't come out
Since it's so...
Use the bomb to destroy the earth
He's fearful of mouse, and became mad
What'll we do now
Doraemon, be calm, it's nothing
The mouse is scared away by you
Really
Great
Find the mouse
when Doraemon doesn't worry
Don't worry Right
I'm back
What're you doing
Mice appeared just now
Dad, what're you saying
Am I wrong Why do you get angry
I really saw them
(Fantastic Pellet)
Let's look for Nobita,
the swimming is funny
I'll take him there
Only I believe he won't go
Who'll pay ten Yuan if he lose
I see
Nobita, let's go to the swimming pool
The swimming pool?
I want to... but I'm reading
Can you read?
You can read later
Nobita, do you want to let me
lose 10 Yuan
Come on
I'll go, wait
How long?
Maybe three years
OK, take out ten Yuan, everybody
I see
For Nobita can't swim
You're cheating! Give me ten Yuan!
I hope I can learn to swim in 3 years
What're you doing
Are you learning to swim?
I made no progress
It's better to go to swim
in the swimming pool
I'll go there after I can swim
You can't swim forever
Really, it's really not OK
Right, would you like this one
The fantastic pellet
What medicine is it?
It can make everything
you want to do come to true
It's so, the fantastic pellet
Come, change it to a swimming pool
Here's swimming pool...
I'll be drowned
Here's the swimming pool
in the kindergarten
The water's shallow
I'm saved
You won't be drowned, begin to practice
The swimming in the kindergarten
is always crowded
Ah, sorry stamp on you
It's troublesome,
why are you always crying
The teacher in the kindergarten
drived me out
Why do you have so much complex thought
OK, regard it as the seaside
I can see the sea
I heard the sound of the wave
We arrived at the seaside
This is the bank
Here's the sand
The offing's there
There's nobody around
Let's make sand castle
Do you come to swim,
dive into the sea quickly
What a big wave, it's terrible
It's shallow here, no problem
Really
I was drowned
It's frightening to swim oneself,
Doraemon, take one fantastic pellet
OK
Let's go out to have a look
It's deeper and deeper
It's a merman
No, it's a goldfish
What'll I do, how can I...
There're many fish
Ah...
There's devilfish too
The fantastic pellet is effective
What a quiet sea
ls it?
I feel there's a whorl beside
Why do you always think bad things
Fortunately its function is over,
we're saved
What're you doing
Let's have this one
Give it to me
OK, let's swim
There's not a swim ring, I want to
have a rest on the island
You're useless
Let me train you
No, no
Your body will come up itself
You needn't the swim ring then
It doesn't come up
You really...
Use this
I found pearl
What It's only a thrown cigarette box
Cull coral
OK, we think there's a sank ship there
It seems there're treasures inside
Are there sharks there?
You sad unlucky words again
It appears
Help!
You won't meet good things
even in the imagining world
You can stay in the sun on the sand
I have the same sense
I'll swim again
Suppose the sun is there
And you're in the sun
Why do you become so black
It's painful...
What a pain“!
Some faces are round
Some faces are long
Some faces are square
Some faces are triangular
Weeping Angry Fawning and Requesting
You'll become a ghost who likes crying
But if you smile
Your face will become round